[{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfe6"},"rt":99599,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":167788,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfe7"},"rt":41643,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209741,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"12D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfe8"},"rt":85885,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":295727,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"3C C F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfe9"},"rt":45636,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":341913,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"02 PM04 PMH 08 AM01 PMU U K K K K J J H H H F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfea"},"rt":84820,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":426839,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfec"},"rt":13450,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":452361,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PME G G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfed"},"rt":45989,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498448,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfee"},"rt":31955,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":530508,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bfef"},"rt":84555,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":615160,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff0"},"rt":17948,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":633398,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff1"},"rt":14081,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":647607,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"M C L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff2"},"rt":43412,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":691117,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff3"},"rt":48712,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":739928,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff4"},"rt":21481,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":761507,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6bff5"},"rt":95969,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":857579,"subject":"R0AON","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5d166d9e3727c40001915aa3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"02 PMC C C C C O 02 PM02 PMX O 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c006"},"rt":31813,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":88605,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c007"},"rt":28321,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117014,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c008"},"rt":12521,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":129680,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c009"},"rt":44259,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174023,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c00a"},"rt":65844,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239997,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c00c"},"rt":7817,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253222,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c00d"},"rt":14014,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":267322,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c00e"},"rt":38445,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":305856,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c00f"},"rt":18369,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":324311,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c010"},"rt":27746,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":352158,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c011"},"rt":10083,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":362333,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c012"},"rt":14039,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":376456,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c013"},"rt":23105,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":399651,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c014"},"rt":10581,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":410316,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c015"},"rt":48532,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":459136,"subject":"CT1PY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d59ab6f7d966eece474824","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c026"},"rt":15434,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50575,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c027"},"rt":25039,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75717,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c028"},"rt":10084,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85910,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c029"},"rt":12434,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":98454,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":"03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c02a"},"rt":6294,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104855,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c02c"},"rt":18141,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":126084,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c02d"},"rt":7558,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134015,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":"05 PM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c02e"},"rt":34144,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":168265,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,E,I,J,K,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c02f"},"rt":20811,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":189181,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G,M","hovered":"J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c030"},"rt":5304,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":194594,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c031"},"rt":14991,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":209695,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c032"},"rt":4462,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214262,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c033"},"rt":47968,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":262336,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N,X","hovered":"02 PMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c034"},"rt":11527,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":273969,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":"01 PM02 PM10 AM05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c035"},"rt":11045,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":285118,"subject":"D7ZC6","study":"SGC4C","session":"su22sona","pool":"sona","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"2218","sona_id":"42780","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c046"},"rt":48017,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154863,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"12 PM11 AMZ Z F F 10 AM09 AM10 AMC 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c047"},"rt":33806,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188848,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"1K D D K 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c048"},"rt":36195,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":225146,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMC 09 AM09 AMC 11 AM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c049"},"rt":11687,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":236926,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"B B H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c04a"},"rt":116931,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":353958,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I I 08 AMO I U U 03 PM02 PMO 02 PMF O 09 AMC 09 AMC C C 10 AMA A F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c04c"},"rt":16257,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377564,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"45E E 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c04d"},"rt":70822,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":448525,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F G B B B B B B B C F B M M M M 12 PMM X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c04e"},"rt":68545,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":517554,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B X X X 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMF B B B B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c04f"},"rt":33059,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":550997,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"J E 09 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c050"},"rt":11908,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":563003,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c051"},"rt":9163,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572267,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM01 PM12 PMM M 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c052"},"rt":8868,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":581231,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c053"},"rt":36798,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":618123,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"09 AMZ Z N N 06 PM04 PMZ Z Z Z F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c054"},"rt":12127,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":630430,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"09 AM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c055"},"rt":65663,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":696191,"subject":"6AVLK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6100e620cb97cef5cc765920","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PM02 PMX K K 09 AMJ 07 PM07 PM06 PM02 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c066"},"rt":44755,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":123617,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O","hovered":"08 AM02 PM04 PM10 AMA A 11 AMA A O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c067"},"rt":30376,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154199,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"K D G G 03 PM02 PMK 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c068"},"rt":19072,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":173321,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMC F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c069"},"rt":44691,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":218067,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"F A O O I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c06a"},"rt":23564,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":241686,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"A H G G 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c06c"},"rt":11584,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":259049,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G 8G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c06d"},"rt":46921,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":306291,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J J J B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c06e"},"rt":55287,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":361628,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"3B J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c06f"},"rt":27516,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":389197,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AMJ 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c070"},"rt":8409,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":397780,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c071"},"rt":13472,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411308,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c072"},"rt":11201,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":422558,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B F 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c073"},"rt":17717,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":440325,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z Z 02 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c074"},"rt":11250,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":451628,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"4512 PM01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c075"},"rt":39590,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":491274,"subject":"395C5","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6114d1493d0852b43237d591","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,G","hovered":"M F 02 PMO C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c086"},"rt":17366,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":93446,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"03 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c087"},"rt":21760,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":115275,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,K","hovered":"O O H D D U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c088"},"rt":40897,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":156254,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C 09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c089"},"rt":16521,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172872,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c08a"},"rt":23521,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":196455,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c08c"},"rt":8743,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":210190,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c08d"},"rt":27166,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":237421,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c08e"},"rt":52412,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289899,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"I B B B B B B B E E 7B F B B G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c08f"},"rt":20022,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":309984,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c090"},"rt":4494,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":314584,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c091"},"rt":8582,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":323235,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c092"},"rt":4426,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327737,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c093"},"rt":9266,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":337071,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c094"},"rt":6306,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":343449,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c095"},"rt":23522,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":367037,"subject":"F1E89","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"X X 02 PMX X X 02 PMC C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0a6"},"rt":47127,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":117574,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,D","hovered":"11 AMA A 2"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0a7"},"rt":19436,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":137203,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0a8"},"rt":21981,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159293,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0a9"},"rt":109559,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268972,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"12 PM12 PM11 AMA A Z Z 12 PM12 PMF F F H H H H 01 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0aa"},"rt":89519,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":359180,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"11 AMA I 03 PM11 AMH A 10 AMF A A 10 AM11 AMZ C C 09 AM09 AM10 AMO 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ac"},"rt":13560,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":377296,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ad"},"rt":23827,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401343,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"11 AMO O X M 09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ae"},"rt":47727,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":449219,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"01 PMX X X G C F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0af"},"rt":37925,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":487257,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11 AMB B J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b0"},"rt":47626,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":535064,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMF B B M F F F E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b1"},"rt":12205,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":547570,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b2"},"rt":8059,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":555980,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b3"},"rt":31766,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":587862,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PMZ F 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b4"},"rt":31366,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619344,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"I F X X X 11 AMM M F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0b5"},"rt":64734,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":684259,"subject":"QOHN7","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e3a7e26ca5cf328020dc4b6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PMX C C F G P G 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0c6"},"rt":8915,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":58701,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"04 PMJ 03 PM11 AMC C 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0c7"},"rt":7601,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66360,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM10 AMU D D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0c8"},"rt":18494,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84910,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AM12 PM01 PMZ C C C C A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0c9"},"rt":49818,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":134774,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,U","hovered":"01 PMZ A Z Z F O O O A 04 PM03 PMU U 12 PM12 PMZ Z F F O 11 AMZ Z I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ca"},"rt":64651,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199517,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMI I I Z I I I I O 11 AM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMU 12 PMG 12 PM10 AMA C A Z Z Z Z F F O O J J J H H H E G 05 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0cc"},"rt":8536,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":216382,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"56G 11 AMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0cd"},"rt":25239,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":241682,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"11 AMB B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ce"},"rt":24384,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":266130,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0cf"},"rt":17064,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283254,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d0"},"rt":35910,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":319226,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d1"},"rt":22482,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":341772,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"03 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d2"},"rt":5610,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":347438,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d3"},"rt":17583,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":365080,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"03 PMZ Z Z X 6"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d4"},"rt":26189,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":391328,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"07 PM03 PM03 PM12 PM11 AMM O E G G L Z 02 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0d5"},"rt":78782,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":470166,"subject":"QGBTT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d6d31b3e2a7f18a131c70c","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"03 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PMB B O O F G G 10 AM01 PM02 PMX 12 PM12 PMM M M 02 PMX X X B B F F 11 AM11 AMC G G X E G G 11 AM15"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0e6"},"rt":11875,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":45990,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"K 12 PM11 AM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0e7"},"rt":15953,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":61980,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"U A A D D D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0e8"},"rt":21584,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":83605,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0e9"},"rt":73445,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157084,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"K A C 01 PM02 PM04 PMB B F K K K G 05 PM04 PMB B B K K Z A U U U U F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ea"},"rt":26585,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183765,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMI "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ec"},"rt":7476,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":195341,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ed"},"rt":19259,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":214636,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"10 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ee"},"rt":14409,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":229077,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0ef"},"rt":24859,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":253972,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f0"},"rt":21692,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":275707,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"01 PMF F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f1"},"rt":13255,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":289003,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"05 PM06 PM07 PM08 PM07 PM06 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM11 AM12 PMM M "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f2"},"rt":66347,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":355384,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PMH F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f3"},"rt":12432,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":367908,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f4"},"rt":39727,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":407689,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"05 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMX X 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c0f5"},"rt":12047,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419773,"subject":"8SWVG","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5909ac7d8aedd80001d3ebb2","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":"03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c106"},"rt":19775,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81453,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c107"},"rt":12890,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94477,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"09 AMO "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c108"},"rt":58034,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":152715,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.25,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,U,B","hovered":"C C C A C C C A U "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c109"},"rt":38072,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190911,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C,U","hovered":"B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c10a"},"rt":22949,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":214057,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"08 AM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c10c"},"rt":13755,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":230829,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c10d"},"rt":14502,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":245471,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c10e"},"rt":50656,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":296258,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"F B B B 08 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c10f"},"rt":24083,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":320469,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c110"},"rt":6921,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":327623,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"F Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c111"},"rt":10618,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":338416,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c112"},"rt":25864,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":364411,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c113"},"rt":56068,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":420685,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":"Z B B 08 AMI F Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c114"},"rt":7637,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":428521,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c115"},"rt":38467,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":467110,"subject":"TTB8O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59c0782e5364260001dc4740","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"12 PMM X N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c126"},"rt":21174,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":205638,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c127"},"rt":15974,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":221801,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c128"},"rt":51826,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":273850,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c129"},"rt":40557,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":314495,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c12a"},"rt":36730,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":351285,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c12c"},"rt":13909,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":369250,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c12d"},"rt":36692,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405996,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c12e"},"rt":91202,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":497252,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.75,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":3,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F,G,O","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c12f"},"rt":54229,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":551649,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c130"},"rt":20734,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":572437,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c131"},"rt":9769,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582294,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c132"},"rt":8412,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":590761,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c133"},"rt":17058,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":607873,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c134"},"rt":11693,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619628,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c135"},"rt":21337,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":641017,"subject":"6YNOF","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5e8f945fe502b12914ae7600","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c146"},"rt":24266,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":192856,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c147"},"rt":16862,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209778,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"O D D D K K 12 PM11 AMD D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c148"},"rt":18967,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":228794,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AMC A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c149"},"rt":74824,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":303675,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"11 AM12 PMU U B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c14a"},"rt":30593,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":334394,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c14c"},"rt":6114,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":344378,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM09 AM08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c14d"},"rt":20773,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":365197,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"11 AMB F B X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c14e"},"rt":54244,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":419491,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMG G C Z Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c14f"},"rt":75834,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":495374,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMB B B B F O O B B J J B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c150"},"rt":54496,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":550001,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"F 5I 08 AMG "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c151"},"rt":10532,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":560581,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c152"},"rt":10295,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":570924,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"O G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c153"},"rt":57491,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":628473,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z H Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c154"},"rt":65693,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":694218,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"09 AMB 08 AMC F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c155"},"rt":38577,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":732920,"subject":"JO5VM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5f94df987e277732aa8e6080","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"02 PMZ Z M 11 AMJ O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c166"},"rt":20491,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":81534,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c167"},"rt":11100,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":92693,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c168"},"rt":27034,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":119783,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AMZ 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c169"},"rt":7431,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127269,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c16a"},"rt":557,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":127885,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c16c"},"rt":1448,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131493,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c16d"},"rt":473,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132022,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c16e"},"rt":401,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":132477,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c16f"},"rt":364,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":132901,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c170"},"rt":439,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":133397,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c171"},"rt":620,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134069,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c172"},"rt":458,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":134580,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c173"},"rt":483,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":135116,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c174"},"rt":516,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":135684,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c175"},"rt":524,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136261,"subject":"7VZMV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"59933524f9db7d000189560e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c186"},"rt":25180,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":80386,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c187"},"rt":15473,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":95928,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"D K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c188"},"rt":12580,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":108655,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"C C 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c189"},"rt":10147,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":118873,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"08 AM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c18a"},"rt":23671,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":142611,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c18c"},"rt":10512,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":158027,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"6E 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c18d"},"rt":24171,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":182259,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c18e"},"rt":52567,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":234906,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"2I B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c18f"},"rt":12345,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":247314,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c190"},"rt":9465,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":256855,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c191"},"rt":11301,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":268216,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM12 PM12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c192"},"rt":6485,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":274770,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c193"},"rt":14217,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":289053,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PMX H Z Z Z 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c194"},"rt":8481,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":297604,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c195"},"rt":27062,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324727,"subject":"YS9FT","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"6296bf32a8a16529919c5790","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X X X K K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1a6"},"rt":25634,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":245117,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1a7"},"rt":12894,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":258094,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1a8"},"rt":13623,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":271800,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1a9"},"rt":79273,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":351151,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1aa"},"rt":102054,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":453449,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I I H H H H H 08 AMA I H Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ac"},"rt":11537,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":473686,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM10 AME "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ad"},"rt":25010,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498783,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"08 AMF J 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ae"},"rt":84692,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":583557,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1af"},"rt":45313,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":629102,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"08 AM11B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b0"},"rt":81562,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":710749,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"10 AMB F Z Z O L C C B B F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b1"},"rt":13440,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":724421,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b2"},"rt":6491,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":731000,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"09 AMJ F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b3"},"rt":54190,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":785267,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMZ 11 AMZ Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b4"},"rt":91506,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":876850,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"11 AMX Z Z O X X L A C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1b5"},"rt":112715,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":989791,"subject":"SSKFO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62d44d484a28cd313e2c3ba4","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PMX X Z Z Z H O O X M M L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1c6"},"rt":36332,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":223449,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"11 AMJ J J H F 11 AM11 AM10 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1c7"},"rt":24586,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":248126,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"D D D D 07 PM06 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1c8"},"rt":19860,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":268214,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"C C C C C Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1c9"},"rt":52380,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":320713,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"05 PM04 PMZ Z A A 11 AM11 AMA F 02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ca"},"rt":93158,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":414029,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM10 AMI I I Z Z 09 AM09 AMC 10 AM10 AM10 AMA 10 AM10 AMA 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1cc"},"rt":10163,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":437212,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"J E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1cd"},"rt":16128,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":453421,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AMB B B B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ce"},"rt":82270,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":536037,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"10 AMB M I E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1cf"},"rt":57219,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":593534,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I","hovered":"E 12 PMB B B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d0"},"rt":71610,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665213,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AMF F F F 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d1"},"rt":26275,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":692049,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"3B 01 PM12 PM12 PMM M M L M M 12 PML L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d2"},"rt":14778,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":707045,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d3"},"rt":122802,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":829916,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"02 PMZ Z 04 PMZ Z Z Z 04 PMB B 12 PME 12G G G 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d4"},"rt":114085,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":944488,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1d5"},"rt":75715,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1020704,"subject":"GC47R","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"616f731019e910895fd75621","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"09 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1e6"},"rt":24718,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122679,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1e7"},"rt":34723,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157632,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1e8"},"rt":26320,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184248,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1e9"},"rt":52801,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":237323,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"09 AMC B 04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ea"},"rt":77412,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":315213,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ec"},"rt":11707,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":350650,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ed"},"rt":50805,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":401698,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ee"},"rt":95235,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":497056,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1ef"},"rt":30435,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":527938,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f0"},"rt":63383,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":591807,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f1"},"rt":13543,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606092,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f2"},"rt":12744,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":619413,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f3"},"rt":91449,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":711114,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f4"},"rt":46688,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":758166,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c1f5"},"rt":67518,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":825957,"subject":"F24DY","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61034c4de28be4c9cd4542c7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c206"},"rt":46710,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":157734,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c207"},"rt":80923,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":238739,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"10 AM11 AMK E E F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c208"},"rt":20623,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":259564,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c209"},"rt":16486,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":276134,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c20a"},"rt":37533,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":313738,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"12 PM01 PM12 PMO O 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c20c"},"rt":72996,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":394693,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM09 AM09 AM09 AM09 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM04 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c20d"},"rt":46675,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":441564,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"11 AM02 PM02 PM01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c20e"},"rt":140469,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":582100,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,G","hovered":"12 PMO O B B B F J 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c20f"},"rt":39612,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":621904,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AMB J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c210"},"rt":27673,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":649665,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c211"},"rt":16161,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665897,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c212"},"rt":12651,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":678619,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"08 AMB F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c213"},"rt":30890,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":709580,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AM12 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c214"},"rt":9111,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":718759,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c215"},"rt":28075,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":746898,"subject":"GXB4O","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62ba066a4093b931382ec48f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"02 PM02 PMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c226"},"rt":22184,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":87105,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"10 AM09 AM11 AMO O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c227"},"rt":9457,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":96628,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"H H D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c228"},"rt":29276,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125971,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"03 PM04 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMC C A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c229"},"rt":48768,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":174809,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,U","hovered":"03 PM12 PM04 PMU Z Z Z F O Z Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c22a"},"rt":68228,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":243105,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"7I 12 PM11 AM12 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c22c"},"rt":10298,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":261855,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c22d"},"rt":15077,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":276996,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c22e"},"rt":38542,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":315602,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMB A 77E I 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c22f"},"rt":25485,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":341191,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"E F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c230"},"rt":51736,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393000,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c231"},"rt":12265,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":405325,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c232"},"rt":7208,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":412597,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c233"},"rt":29564,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442226,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c234"},"rt":41126,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":483414,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"J J B B 07 PM12 PM12 PMX A A H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c235"},"rt":58195,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":541669,"subject":"2CJ7D","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"62b1f2bfcec5a48852005c5f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"P O 01 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c246"},"rt":34271,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":104883,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AM110 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c247"},"rt":26812,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131783,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"08 AMC C C O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c248"},"rt":21990,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153851,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMC C 10 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c249"},"rt":10951,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164881,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"03 PM05 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c24a"},"rt":45312,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":210268,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"09 AMA I I U 1I 308 AMI 3109 AM11 AM12 PMZ 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c24c"},"rt":8992,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":224974,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PME 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c24d"},"rt":70495,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295545,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"J 6E I I I J J J J I M M 01 PM01 PMM M 01 PMM M M I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c24e"},"rt":122462,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":418450,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"67X E B J J J B J B B N N N B B B 10 AM10 AMB 10 AMF F F E E E G J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c24f"},"rt":41176,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460098,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J I E I I I J J 11 AMJ I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c250"},"rt":11337,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":471515,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"10 AMF 02 PM02 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c251"},"rt":16395,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487982,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"01 PM01 PM12 PMM M M M 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c252"},"rt":12147,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":500212,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"F F F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c253"},"rt":22369,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":522667,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"X Z Z 02 PMZ Z 01 PM02 PMF 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c254"},"rt":15072,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":537818,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"03 PMX 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c255"},"rt":69719,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":607618,"subject":"1EOUS","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"5ef0bafa11382411c231af32","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L","hovered":"01 PM02 PM12 PM12 PMM M L L L L "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c266"},"rt":24292,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":66166,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AMA Z F A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c267"},"rt":8829,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75042,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c268"},"rt":8973,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84064,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c269"},"rt":5264,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":89372,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c26a"},"rt":21326,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110747,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"I O 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c26c"},"rt":15999,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":131126,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AME G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c26d"},"rt":16814,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":147983,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"01 PMX O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c26e"},"rt":42441,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":190471,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"12 PMF F G G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c26f"},"rt":42670,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":233232,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c270"},"rt":6395,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":239671,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F F 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c271"},"rt":10439,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":250157,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c272"},"rt":6994,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":257194,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"11 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c273"},"rt":26263,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":283500,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AMZ Z Z 03 PM02 PM02 PMZ Z 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c274"},"rt":16289,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":299832,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c275"},"rt":22454,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":322329,"subject":"SV20G","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62962188ab5037f57b743543","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PMX X K K 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c286"},"rt":65974,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":199294,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AMF 10 AM12 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM10 AM11 AMZ F F F 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c287"},"rt":31078,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":230705,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"11 AMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c288"},"rt":23125,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":254012,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"09 AMC "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c289"},"rt":35118,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":289275,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"10 AMB H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c28a"},"rt":33784,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":323209,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"I O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c28c"},"rt":12284,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":343750,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c28d"},"rt":91978,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":435876,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"J F F F B I I I I I B B M M M M X X O X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c28e"},"rt":51131,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487342,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"10 AMB B B F F F X X F G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c28f"},"rt":28113,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":515614,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AMJ J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c290"},"rt":50113,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":565900,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c291"},"rt":8585,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":574623,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"12 PMM "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c292"},"rt":12526,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":587293,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"09 AMB 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c293"},"rt":33266,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":620700,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"12 PMZ Z X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c294"},"rt":31659,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":652502,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c295"},"rt":85458,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":738097,"subject":"T7NPC","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"566a1d697da0350005b39de3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,X","hovered":"01 PMZ Z Z Z H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2a6"},"rt":53701,"condition":"113112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":125348,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA 09 AM10 AM11 AMA 11 AM11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2a7"},"rt":21435,"condition":"113112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146842,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"01 PMK K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2a8"},"rt":84697,"condition":"113112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":231565,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,Z","hovered":"10 AMC C C C A C C C C Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2a9"},"rt":103871,"condition":"113112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":335525,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM02 PM01 PMC C C A A 03 PM02 PMZ U U 10 AMX 12 PM02 PMF F F O O O I O 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2aa"},"rt":67877,"condition":"113112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":403493,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H,F","hovered":"12 PMI 08 AM09 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PMI 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ac"},"rt":20270,"condition":"113112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":430447,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ad"},"rt":23042,"condition":"113112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":453513,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ae"},"rt":62942,"condition":"113112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":516475,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B X X 11 AME 608 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2af"},"rt":87285,"condition":"113112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":603839,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"09 AMB I E J 10 AM11 AMB B B B I 10 AMG 11 AMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b0"},"rt":46675,"condition":"113112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":650598,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":"12 PMB B F F B 12 PM11 AM09 AMI 08 AM09 AMJ 11 AM11 AMJ 10 AM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b1"},"rt":14382,"condition":"113112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":665000,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMF F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b2"},"rt":18941,"condition":"113112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":683962,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PMF B B B G G 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b3"},"rt":67067,"condition":"113112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":751059,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"12 PMZ Z Z 04 PM12 PM09 AMI E 11 AMB J J J B B B B 11 AMM X X X 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b4"},"rt":43998,"condition":"113112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":795148,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM11 AMJ B B B B B F F B B M X X C C C G 01 PMG G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2b5"},"rt":19538,"condition":"113112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"3","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":814710,"subject":"0TUJO","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d78f270296bdf7e6cf9515","sona_id":"60e9c78a617cbabf4732fee6","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM01 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2c6"},"rt":53196,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":109147,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AMC 02 PM11 AMF 11 AMC 11 AM10 AMA A A A A A F A A A A A A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2c7"},"rt":22050,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":131255,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B U F F D D E 04 PMD E E E 04 PM04 PME E D E E 03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2c8"},"rt":51754,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":183067,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"Z C C C C 10 AMC C C 11 AM10 AM10 AM10 AMC A Z Z Z Z Z Z Z Z F Z 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2c9"},"rt":37622,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":220738,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C F 04 PM02 PM01 PMC C U 03 PM02 PM01 PM12 PMZ U U U U 01 PM02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ca"},"rt":77164,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":297964,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A 10 AMC 10 AMC O I I 108 AMI O O O I 1"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2cc"},"rt":10253,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":313870,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AMG E 3"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2cd"},"rt":16303,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":330225,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J J B B B B F F F B B B B B F 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ce"},"rt":25853,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":356124,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"B B O O O X B B B E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2cf"},"rt":16060,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":372235,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d0"},"rt":41841,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":414128,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"10 AMF F F B B 12 PMB B F B B B B B F E F X F M X F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d1"},"rt":12992,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":427184,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"G G 12 PMB B F B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d2"},"rt":3770,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431009,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d3"},"rt":29199,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460259,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z Z 04 PMZ Z Z Z O X 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d4"},"rt":52449,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":512756,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"04 PMO C F B J J I E E 03 PM02 PM02 PM03 PMC F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2d5"},"rt":46210,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":559014,"subject":"4EDBK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c38b8983f0660c9aa0db5","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"10 AMB B B B B B B B B F 09 AMZ F F E 1C X 12 PMM 01 PM12 PM12 PMJ J I I B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2e6"},"rt":68731,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204585,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"08 AM11 AMA 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2e7"},"rt":37992,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":242808,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2e8"},"rt":32169,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":275051,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I","hovered":"0C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2e9"},"rt":44827,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":319944,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"02 PM04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ea"},"rt":79078,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":399095,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J,D","hovered":"11 AMI I Z 12 PM12 PM11 AM11 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ec"},"rt":12007,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":419543,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"01 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ed"},"rt":35718,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":455327,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ee"},"rt":150924,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":606320,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"E 09 AMF F C B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2ef"},"rt":46324,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":652863,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"10 AMJ B B B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f0"},"rt":69784,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":722712,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"11 AMF 05 PM04 PM04 PM10 AM02 PMN H H F H Z Z 04 PMZ Z 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f1"},"rt":16255,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739232,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f2"},"rt":10695,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":749999,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f3"},"rt":56157,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":806224,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"H Z Z X 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f4"},"rt":143296,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":949583,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PM03 PM02 PMX X X X M X 03 PME E G G X M M J X B 09 AM12 PMF "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c2f5"},"rt":74635,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1024439,"subject":"GV92N","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5cbc97cd214b1a0001ccfa53","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PM11 AM03 PM03 PM02 PM02 PMC 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c306"},"rt":38174,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186749,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c307"},"rt":17584,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":204392,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c308"},"rt":29274,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":233722,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c309"},"rt":74021,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":307802,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c30a"},"rt":112127,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":420188,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"11 AMK I 09 AM12 PM01 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c30c"},"rt":13089,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442054,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"05 PM08 AMG B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c30d"},"rt":19554,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":461669,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c30e"},"rt":109684,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":571409,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AME F F B B 09 AM10 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM11 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c30f"},"rt":16524,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":588223,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c310"},"rt":63318,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":651597,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"F F F B B 12 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c311"},"rt":9184,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":661266,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c312"},"rt":9570,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":670892,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c313"},"rt":19433,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":690392,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c314"},"rt":48843,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":739292,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c315"},"rt":100108,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":839466,"subject":"67Z0V","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"611285de4477f8152efce6e8","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c326"},"rt":7427,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":29107,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c327"},"rt":7686,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":36873,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c328"},"rt":6756,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":43706,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c329"},"rt":6861,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":50641,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c32a"},"rt":8550,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":59264,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.9166666666666666,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O","hovered":"I I I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c32c"},"rt":5035,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":66539,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c32d"},"rt":11473,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":78093,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"E O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c32e"},"rt":14513,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":92677,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c32f"},"rt":28491,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":121247,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I J J J J J J J B 10 AM10 AMB B B 01 PMM J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c330"},"rt":5658,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":126980,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c331"},"rt":4775,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":131831,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c332"},"rt":4226,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":136131,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c333"},"rt":8149,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":144348,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c334"},"rt":5849,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":150265,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c335"},"rt":14412,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":164750,"subject":"UEETV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62d7858e9d0bb849183e1500","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c346"},"rt":49681,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":179856,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c347"},"rt":8068,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188306,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c348"},"rt":12444,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":201110,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c349"},"rt":19677,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":221148,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c34a"},"rt":57763,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":279270,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c34c"},"rt":22282,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":310405,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c34d"},"rt":36052,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346817,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c34e"},"rt":64486,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":411639,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"G C C O O X E B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c34f"},"rt":36377,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":449121,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I 05 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c350"},"rt":22918,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":472381,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c351"},"rt":9449,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":482186,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"N","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c352"},"rt":16194,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":498724,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c353"},"rt":74369,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":573436,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,O","hovered":"Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c354"},"rt":52865,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":628157,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"P","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c355"},"rt":34702,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":663202,"subject":"L5L85","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"62cf3efe6b75b1e4ee3c372f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.33333333333333337,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,K,L","hovered":"02 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c366"},"rt":24041,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":146092,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"12 PMA A 11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c367"},"rt":13212,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":159353,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMD "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c368"},"rt":12931,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":172338,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c369"},"rt":15858,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":188256,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"104 PM04 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM01 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c36a"},"rt":23112,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":211426,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"3F I I O O 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c36c"},"rt":42932,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":291616,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"09 AM08 AM09 AM08 AMC C 10 AM11 AM02 PMB 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c36d"},"rt":62561,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":354238,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c36e"},"rt":85682,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":440080,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"B B B M M M M 12 PM11 AMM B B B M M X X O O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c36f"},"rt":20635,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":460866,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"09 AMJ J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c370"},"rt":34577,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":495502,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F B B F F F F 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c371"},"rt":65599,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":561160,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":6,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,H,L,M,N,O,Z,X","hovered":"09 AM02 PM03 PMM G C C M M C L 01 PM11 AMX O H H X O O O Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c372"},"rt":32721,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":594028,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c373"},"rt":53392,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":647507,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"O N Z X H Z Z Z 02 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c374"},"rt":10444,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":658009,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"M 02 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c375"},"rt":22913,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":680980,"subject":"MLNH1","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"627ad907d485eb4e0546a534","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.4166666666666667,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"C,X","hovered":"01 PM02 PM02 PMX X C C 01 PMC C 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c386"},"rt":41259,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":208316,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"12 PMF 09 AM09 AM11 AM11 AMK Z 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c387"},"rt":31340,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":239732,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"05 PMZ 11 AM03 PMD 12 PMU 08 PMG B 06 PM08 PME 11 AM10 AM11 AMZ Z K K "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c388"},"rt":30235,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":270041,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"02 PMC C 11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c389"},"rt":30617,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":300739,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"11 AM01 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM10 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c38a"},"rt":28437,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":329254,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"09 AMI I O 12 PM12 PMZ Z F F 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c38c"},"rt":18978,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":352404,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"G 01 PMC 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c38d"},"rt":27172,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":379652,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"X X O 12 PM01 PMX O O X 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c38e"},"rt":96665,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":476396,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0.8333333333333334,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,G,K","hovered":"02G G C C F B F B B 10 AM10 AMX 03 PM03 PM03 PM10 AMB B P P B F B P P B 10 AM10 AMF P B O 04 PM04 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM03 PMX X B B 10 AM10 AMF F C 10 AMB P P P G G K K K I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c38f"},"rt":42112,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":518731,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"O O 10 AM10 AM10 AMB 10 AMF F F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c390"},"rt":14336,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":533142,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c391"},"rt":20389,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":553604,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"02 PM01 PML "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c392"},"rt":8670,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":562351,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c393"},"rt":16269,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":578696,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c394"},"rt":10642,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":589420,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c395"},"rt":38806,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":628299,"subject":"0PAWH","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5f107aa051372032695c8e2f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"K 02 PM12 PMX 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3a6"},"rt":11632,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":94795,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3a7"},"rt":15453,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":110304,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"Z D G E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3a8"},"rt":18499,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":128854,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"A C Z Z Z 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3a9"},"rt":57868,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":186774,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"01 PMF 3F 02 PM04 PM04 PM01 PMU U 10 AMA O O 12 PM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3aa"},"rt":25659,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":212483,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"02 PM11 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ac"},"rt":9013,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":226793,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ad"},"rt":22138,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":248983,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ae"},"rt":28943,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":277978,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"08 AMB B B B 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3af"},"rt":10786,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":288896,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"01 PMJ J J J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b0"},"rt":57070,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":346012,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"12 PMF F B B Z J J J J J E E 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b1"},"rt":11596,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":357659,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b2"},"rt":35367,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":393074,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b3"},"rt":49778,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":442920,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,N","hovered":"D Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b4"},"rt":46455,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":489421,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3b5"},"rt":25444,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514916,"subject":"O9T8H","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6168dd1b3907260e72c43837","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3c6"},"rt":51889,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":154353,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,O,I","hovered":"09 AM09 AM11 AM11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3c7"},"rt":30386,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":184844,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3c8"},"rt":38881,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":223825,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3c9"},"rt":97893,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":321812,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,U","hovered":"O K 12 PM12 PM02 PM04 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM09 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ca"},"rt":69102,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":391128,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10 AM12 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3cc"},"rt":74122,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":485172,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"01 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3cd"},"rt":29565,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":514936,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AMF 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ce"},"rt":49760,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564797,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3cf"},"rt":35288,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":600190,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"09 AM10 AM10 AM11 AM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d0"},"rt":98535,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":698825,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM10 AMM 01 PM12 PM12 PM12 PM11 AM12 PM11 AM12 PM12 PM12 PM01 PM01 PM01 PM02 PM03 PM0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d1"},"rt":19321,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":718355,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d2"},"rt":18202,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":736655,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d3"},"rt":57698,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":794457,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,O","hovered":"10 AMX O 03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM12 PM01 PM02 PM02 PM03 PM02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d4"},"rt":39992,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":834554,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"01 PMX X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3d5"},"rt":40974,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":875629,"subject":"SCB5T","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6296267b2ae249a205d319d3","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3e6"},"rt":16455,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":55992,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3e7"},"rt":19286,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":75370,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K","hovered":"08 AMZ 01 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM05 PM04 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3e8"},"rt":9721,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":85190,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F","hovered":"08 AMC C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3e9"},"rt":37161,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":122452,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"H","hovered":"12 PM11 AM12 PM01 PMH H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ea"},"rt":55330,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":177879,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AMC I C A O F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ec"},"rt":8229,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":199094,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ed"},"rt":16239,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":215420,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"F O O 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ee"},"rt":38339,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":253850,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"E G 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3ef"},"rt":17163,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":271104,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"J J J I 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f0"},"rt":16662,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":287864,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"F F J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f1"},"rt":6504,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":294471,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"L,M","hovered":"10 AM10 AM11 AM10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f2"},"rt":6351,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":300908,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"G","hovered":"J B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f3"},"rt":13106,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":314102,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0.5,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"Z E E 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f4"},"rt":9812,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":324005,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c3f5"},"rt":72439,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":396546,"subject":"YZN1M","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5e433ee571d7421d7e44d259","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":"J 11 AM11 AM11 AM12 PM01 PMX 02 PM01 PM12 PM11 AM11 AMC C X 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c406"},"rt":61983,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":282680,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c407"},"rt":24553,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":307492,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c408"},"rt":62424,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":370184,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":1,"answer":"","hovered":"0A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c409"},"rt":19290,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":389752,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c40a"},"rt":103853,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":493863,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,Z","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c40c"},"rt":29297,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":532704,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c40d"},"rt":31403,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":564365,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c40e"},"rt":116526,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":681139,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"J","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c40f"},"rt":20186,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":702641,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c410"},"rt":100929,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":803976,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"M","hovered":"01 PMF F F B B M M M B B O B O O O B B 2X X N "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c411"},"rt":18767,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":823062,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c412"},"rt":11829,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":835017,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c413"},"rt":27818,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":862972,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"Z F F B B O X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c414"},"rt":195658,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1058765,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"02 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c415"},"rt":34363,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":1093432,"subject":"WHNRQ","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"5a202eda7413810001521ac7","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A,C","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c426"},"rt":16633,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":71775,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"11 AM11 AMA A A 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c427"},"rt":13183,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":84994,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"D E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c428"},"rt":41506,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":126537,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"O U A Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c429"},"rt":26575,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":153145,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM12 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM12 PM02 PM03 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c42a"},"rt":11350,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":164531,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c42c"},"rt":8776,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":180827,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"E 36"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c42d"},"rt":25807,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":206667,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"08 AM0J X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c42e"},"rt":40194,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":246894,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,I,J","hovered":"J B B B 08 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c42f"},"rt":23963,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":270892,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11 AMI B J 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c430"},"rt":24270,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":295194,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"Z Z 01 PM11 AMB B Z Z 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c431"},"rt":9437,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":304664,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"02 PM12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c432"},"rt":5847,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":310544,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c433"},"rt":27378,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":337958,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"08 AMJ M H Z Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c434"},"rt":20758,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":358750,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AMJ 03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c435"},"rt":35941,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":394732,"subject":"0KDXV","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"610c0b8627771f98c5ee375f","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"G G M M 02 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c446"},"rt":35303,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":114511,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"010 AM09 AM08 AM09 AMA A A A A Z 01 PM02 PM01 PM11 AM11 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c447"},"rt":54118,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":168685,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"A A D D E E E E D D D D D E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c448"},"rt":21811,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190548,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"O C C 10 AMC Z Z Z Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c449"},"rt":39536,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":230137,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"C C C C A A Z Z Z Z Z Z Z U F U U U F Z F F O O O O O 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c44a"},"rt":258000,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":488189,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"09 AM08 AM09 AMJ J I I I O 11 AMI O O I "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c44c"},"rt":12824,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":551374,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"08 AME E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c44d"},"rt":16189,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":567615,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"F F B B B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c44e"},"rt":46774,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":614448,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"02 PMB 12 PME E 11 AM05 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c44f"},"rt":13765,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":628262,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"08 AMM X B J J I B 09 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c450"},"rt":43519,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":671837,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"F F B B 12 PM01 PM02 PM04 PM04 PMO X O "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c451"},"rt":7759,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":679652,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"J 12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c452"},"rt":26450,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":706157,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"F B B B 08 AMJ F F B B 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c453"},"rt":19758,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":725971,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"3F F H Z Z Z Z Z 04 PM04 PM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c454"},"rt":55567,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":781593,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"G F X X 03 PM12 PMM B F B B 12 PMJ J E 02 PM05 PM05 PM04 PM11 AM10 AMJ J M M X X O O C A G 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c455"},"rt":64232,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":845882,"subject":"GD2OK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"60fd6607e7beec3c98d994b1","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,X","hovered":"08 AM09 AM12 PM02 PMB 01 PMM B F F E E E G X X C 01 PMX X 01 PMX "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c466"},"rt":45539,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":190101,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PMZ 11 AM10 AM11 AMA A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c467"},"rt":26092,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":216326,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.0833333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"11 AM04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c468"},"rt":49026,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":265614,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"09 AM10 AMF F F F A A "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c469"},"rt":21897,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":287955,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.16666666666666666,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"D,E","hovered":"10 AM04 PM04 PM04 PME E E D "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c46a"},"rt":21181,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":309370,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O","hovered":"10 AMI O O O 12 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c46c"},"rt":13777,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":329607,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"008 AM09 AM6E G "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c46d"},"rt":21768,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":351646,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,Z","hovered":"F F Z "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c46e"},"rt":79764,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":431543,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"11 AMJ J F F F F F B "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c46f"},"rt":21999,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":453862,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"I I 0"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c470"},"rt":14372,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":468374,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.08333333333333333,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":0,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"Z","hovered":"H H "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c471"},"rt":19417,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":487939,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"01 PM12 PMB B F "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c472"},"rt":16287,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":504451,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"09 AMB B B 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c473"},"rt":144452,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":649200,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5833333333333334,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":1,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,X","hovered":"03 PMC L H O N Z Z Z 04 PMZ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c474"},"rt":69944,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":719474,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c475"},"rt":21720,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":741528,"subject":"7C7KM","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"61010400617800821cac834e","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":1,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":0,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"K,X","hovered":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c486"},"rt":32620,"condition":"111112","q":1,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 11 am?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":209262,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"A","hovered":"12 PM12 PM10 AM11 AM11 AM11 AMA A A A A 11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c487"},"rt":10049,"condition":"111112","q":2,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as D?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":219421,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"01 PMF F D D E E 04 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c488"},"rt":84541,"condition":"111112","q":3,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begin when C ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":304070,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1.1666666666666667,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":2,"blank_score":0,"answer":"O,I,Z","hovered":"09 AMC C A C C 10 AMA "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c489"},"rt":117937,"condition":"111112","q":4,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 4 pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":422290,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PM12 PM11 AMC A A U U U U U U U I I I U 04 PMH H H H 01 PMH U U U U 01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c48a"},"rt":140375,"condition":"111112","q":5,"explicit":"1","impasse":"1","grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift.</br> Which shift(s) share a break with I?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_control","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_scaffold","time_elapsed":562931,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"U","hovered":"01 PMI I O O 03 PM08 AMO Z Z Z Z F F I 03 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c48c"},"rt":15327,"condition":"111112","q":6,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) are six hours long?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":601837,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":2,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,G","hovered":"11 AMJ "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c48d"},"rt":24560,"condition":"111112","q":7,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts less than 5 hours long start at the same time?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":626524,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"10 AM11 AMB B M M 08 AMB B B B B 10 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c48e"},"rt":50785,"condition":"111112","q":8,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) under 7 hours long starts before B starts, and ends after X ends?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"duration+contained","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":677420,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E","hovered":"04 PMB B X X X N X X B B B J J J F E E "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c48f"},"rt":20672,"condition":"111112","q":9,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) begins before J begins and ends during B?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime+before+endtime+during","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":698196,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":true,"discriminant":0,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"I","hovered":"11 AMJ J "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c490"},"rt":16652,"condition":"111112","q":10,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"ends","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":714956,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"X","hovered":"12 PMM F B B 12 PMF X "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c491"},"rt":10516,"condition":"111112","q":11,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at 12pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starttime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":725582,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B,F","hovered":"12 PMB "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c492"},"rt":8573,"condition":"111112","q":12,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) start at the same time as F?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"starts","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":734262,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"11 AM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c493"},"rt":38984,"condition":"111112","q":13,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which 2 shifts end when Z begins?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"meets","block":"item_nondiscriminant","time_elapsed":773372,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-0.5,"tri_score":1,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"F,X","hovered":"01 PMZ Z 04 PMB B B B B B X X B M M M B B O X X X X 02 PM02 PM01 PM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c494"},"rt":23376,"condition":"111112","q":14,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Which shift(s) end at 3pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"endtime","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":796859,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":1,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"B","hovered":"03 PM03 PMX X 09 AMF F F B I E E C C C C "},{"_id":{"$oid":"62db5d06d2276416d6f6c495"},"rt":58399,"condition":"111112","q":15,"explicit":"1","impasse":1,"grid":"1","mark":"1","ixn":"1","rotation":"2","question":"Coffee breaks happen halfway through a shift. </br>Which shifts share a break at 2pm?","graph":"triangular","datafile":"acme_main","colorClick":false,"gwidth":600,"gheight":600,"relation":"midpoint","block":"item_test","time_elapsed":855365,"subject":"CBCXK","study":"SGC4C","session":"suPROLIFIC","pool":"prolific","mode":"asynch","exp_id":"62d846e008ffdac5ea24b94e","sona_id":"6075ff702ca9dd94767cca11","source":"limitless-plains","correct":false,"discriminant":-1,"tri_score":0,"orth_score":2,"other_score":0,"blank_score":0,"answer":"E,F","hovered":"02 PMX X X X 0C O G E 11 AMA G "}]
